<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PPAB_RecycleView</string>
    <array name="list_deskripsi">
        <item>Revolutionary thinking is at the heart of every idea from Automobili Lamborghini. Whether it is aerospace-inspired design or technologies applied to the naturally aspirated V12 engine or carbon-fiber structure, going beyond accepted limits is part of our philosophy. The Aventador advances every concept of performance, immediately establishing itself as the benchmark for the super sports car sector. Giving a glimpse of the future today, it comes from a family of supercars already considered legendary.
        </item>

        <item>Nine conceptual design studies were considered for the V12 hybrid flagship in 2011, reduced to five in April 2011 (three by Ferrari Centro Stile and two by Pininfarina). Of these, two full-size concepts were built: LaFerrari Concept Manta (internal designation: 2011 Model 2) and LaFerrari Concept Tensostruttura (internal designation 2011 Model 3). These were unveiled at the Ferrari Museum in Maranello, Italy and Ferrari World in Abu Dhabi. The final design of LaFerrari is similar to the Manta concept (Model 2).
        </item>

        <item>The Toyota Supra (Japanese: トヨタ・スープラ, Hepburn: Toyota Sūpura) is a sports car and grand tourer manufactured by the Toyota Motor Corporation beginning in 1978. The name "supra" is derived from the Latin prefix, meaning "above", "to surpass" or "go beyond".
        </item>

        <item>The Pagani Zonda is a mid-engine sports car produced by Italian sports car manufacturer Pagani. It debuted at the 1999 Geneva Motor Show. Produced on commission in limited units, as of 2019 a total of 140 cars had been built, including development mules. Variants include a 2-door coupé and roadster variant, along with a third new variant being the barchetta. Construction is mainly of carbon fibre.
        </item>

        <item>The Bugatti Veyron EB 16.4 is a mid-engine sports car, designed and developed in Germany by the Volkswagen Group and Bugatti and manufactured in Molsheim, France, by French automobile manufacturer Bugatti. It was named after the racing driver Pierre Veyron. The original version has a top speed of 407 km/h (253 mph).[5][6] It was named the 2000s Car of the Decade by the BBC television programme Top Gear. The standard Veyron also won Top Gear\'s Best Car Driven All Year award in 2005.
        </item>

        <item>The Porsche 911 (pronounced Nine Eleven or in German: Neunelf) is a two-door 2+2 high performance rear-engined sports car introduced in September 1964 by Porsche AG of Stuttgart, Germany. It has a rear-mounted flat-six engine and originally a torsion bar suspension. The car has been continuously enhanced through the years but the basic concept has remained unchanged.[1] The engines were air-cooled until the introduction of the 996 series in 1998.
        </item>

        <item>The Bugatti Veyron EB 16.4 is a mid-engine sports car, designed and developed in Germany by the Volkswagen Group and Bugatti and manufactured in Molsheim, France, by French automobile manufacturer Bugatti. It was named after the racing driver Pierre Veyron. The original version has a top speed of 407 km/h (253 mph).[5][6] It was named the 2000s Car of the Decade by the BBC television programme Top Gear. The standard Veyron also won Top Gear\'s Best Car Driven All Year award in 2005.
        </item>

        <item>The Bugatti Veyron EB 16.4 is a mid-engine sports car, designed and developed in Germany by the Volkswagen Group and Bugatti and manufactured in Molsheim, France, by French automobile manufacturer Bugatti. It was named after the racing driver Pierre Veyron. The original version has a top speed of 407 km/h (253 mph).[5][6] It was named the 2000s Car of the Decade by the BBC television programme Top Gear. The standard Veyron also won Top Gear\'s Best Car Driven All Year award in 2005.
        </item>

        <item>The Bugatti Veyron EB 16.4 is a mid-engine sports car, designed and developed in Germany by the Volkswagen Group and Bugatti and manufactured in Molsheim, France, by French automobile manufacturer Bugatti. It was named after the racing driver Pierre Veyron. The original version has a top speed of 407 km/h (253 mph).[5][6] It was named the 2000s Car of the Decade by the BBC television programme Top Gear. The standard Veyron also won Top Gear\'s Best Car Driven All Year award in 2005.
        </item>

    </array>
</resources>